https://mmoui.com/?privacy

Sites
About
Contact
Privacy Statement
The MMOUI Website (www.mmoui.com)
is maintained by Good Game Mods, LLC. Protecting your privacy is important to Good Game Mods, LLC, and this statement is intended to make you aware of our
commitments to you as an important visitor to our website. This policy may
change from time to time, so please check back periodically.
1.
Scope of the Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies only to the collection and use of
information collected online on the Good Game Mods, LLC Website. Other websites
that may be affiliated with Good Game Mods, LLC may have different privacy
policies.
2.
Information. We may collect your personally identifiable information
("Personal Information") when you visit the Good Game Mods, LLC Website. Personal
Information, however, is not collected on this website unless you choose to
provide it to us. When making inquiries, ordering a product or requesting
service information, participating in certain promotional activities, completing
surveys, and generally corresponding with us, we may ask for certain Personal
Information, including, for example, your name, mailing address, phone number
and email address. If you are on a part of our website that requires you to
provide your Personal Information, it will be clear what Personal Information
we are requesting. We may also collect other information that is provided to us
by your web browser. This may include the browser you used to come to our
website, the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website that you just
visited before visiting our website, which pages on our website you visit, any
search terms you entered, which URL you go to next, and your Internet Protocol
("IP") address.
3.
Use of your information. Information is collected and used in various ways that will help
us better serve our customers and visitors to our website, including those
below.
1.
Browsing. Information collected while browsing through our website. This
information is collected to help run our site more efficiently, to gather broad
demographic information, to monitor the level of activity on our site, and to
evaluate the effectiveness of advertising and promotion.
2.
Product Inquiries, Placing
Orders, Customer Service & Technical Support. Information collected when you contact Good Game Mods, LLC about our
product and service offerings. This information is necessary to identify your
products or systems, understand the configuration of the products, diagnose
your questions, and provide solutions.
3.
Online surveys and polling. Information collected you volunteer to complete surveys or
participate in polls. Surveying and polling is extremely important to us as we
use this information to improve our product and service offerings.
4.
Promotional activities. When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask you for
information such as your name, address and e-mail address to administer the
program or activity, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners and make
the winners' list publicly available in compliance with laws which may apply to
such activities.
5.
Newsletters and promotional
e-mails. As a service to our customers,
we may e-mail you newsletters, promotional information and other information,
using your Personal Information collected online. These e-mails will only be sent to you if you have agreed to receive them and
you have the right to opt out from further receiving them.
6.
Contact information: If you contact us, we may keep a record of your correspondence or
comments, including any information therein. We use this information to help us
provide better service.
7.
Sharing your Personal
Information. Unless we have your permission to do otherwise, we will share
the Personal Information you provide online only with Good Game Mods, LLC
subsidiaries or affiliates or with entities that provide services to Good Game Mods, LLC or are business partners of Good Game Mods, LLC, and only for
legitimate purposes including those described herein. Personal Information we
collect online is used for responding to inquiries, processing orders, keeping
you informed about your order status, for statistical purposes, for improving
our site and its performance, for developing better products and services, to
serve advertisements, contests, surveys and promotions, and to notify you of
products or special offers that may be of interest to you. Good Game Mods, LLC (or
part of it) or its related entities could merge with or be acquired by another
business entity or their respective assets could be acquired. Should such a
combination or acquisition occur, you should expect that Good Game Mods, LLC would
share some or all of your Personal Information to continue serving you and
other users of our website. Occasionally, we may be required by law enforcement
or judicial authorities to provide your Personal Information to the appropriate
authorities. We will disclose your Personal Information if required by law,
upon receipt of a court order or subpoena, or to cooperate with a law
enforcement investigation. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement
authorities any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful.
8.
Use of cookies and web beacons.
1.
Cookies. A "cookie" is a small data file that a website can send to your
browser, which may then be stored on your system. We use cookies to better
serve you when you return to our site. Some of our web pages may send cookies
when you visit our site, make purchases, respond to online surveys or
promotions, participate in a contest, or request information. Accepting the
cookies used on our site enables our web server to identify your system by
reading the cookie that has been stored on your system, but our web server
cannot identify you unless you enter your Personal Information. Cookies that
are placed when visiting our site cannot be used to obtain your Personal
Information at another site. The information collected online permits us to
analyze traffic patterns on our site. This can enable us over time to provide
users with a better experience on our site by improving the content and making
it easier to use. Depending on the browser used, you can set your browser to
notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether
to accept it, and you can also set your browser to turn off cookies. However,
if you do so, some areas of this site may not function properly, or you will be
required to re-enter your Personal Information to use an area of this site.
2.
Web Beacons. We may also use web beacon technologies to better tailor the site
to provide better customer service. A web beacon is a single pixel .GIF that
allows a website to count users who have visited that page or access certain
cookies. These web beacons may be placed on specific pages across this website.
When a visitor accesses these pages, an anonymous notice of that visit is
generated which may be processed by us or by our vendors. These web beacons
work in conjunction with cookies. If you don't want to associate your anonymous
cookie information with your visits to these pages, depending on the browser
used, you can set your browser to turn off cookies.
4.
Children's privacy. If you are under the age of 18, please make sure that you provide
your Personal Information only after obtaining your parental consent.
5.
Protecting your Personal
Information. While Good Game Mods, LLC does
not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur, Good Game Mods, LLC does take care in maintaining the security of your
Personal Information and in preventing unauthorized access to it.
6.
Links to other Websites. Parts of our site contain links to our subsidiaries, affiliates
and third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you use these
links, you will leave Good Game Mods, LLC's website. When you access these other
sites, even ones that may contain the Good Game Mods, LLC mark, please understand
that we do not control the content and are not responsible for the privacy
practices of that website. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy
policies of each website you visit. This Online Privacy Statement does not
cover the information practices of those websites linked to our site. These
other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit
Personal Information.
7.
Changes to this Statement. Good Game Mods, LLC reserves the right to change this Online Privacy
Statement at any time. Any such changes will be posted in this Privacy
Statement.
8.
Applicable laws. Good Game Mods, LLC will protect your Personal Information in
accordance with the laws of the United States and the state of Delaware.
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. to learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.
Privacy Policy - Terms of Service - Advertise
© 2002 - 2020 MMOUI
